(Leonard:)Here you go, Copenhagen boy.
(Leonard:)How about a taste
of Hans Christian hand grenade?
[EXPLOSION ON TV]
[MOUTHING]
LEONARD:
That could not feel good.
(Leonard:)Come on, come on. Oh, you clever...
(Leonard:)Come on, come on.
(Leonard:)Take that.
Uh-oh.
[SHOUTING]
- What's the matter?
- This granola bar has peanuts in it.
- Oh, my God. Why did you eat it?
- I don't know, it was just there.
(Leonard:)Well, if I had a gun there,
would you have shot yourself?
(Howard:)Don't yell at me.
- I've gotta go to the emergency room.
- Now?
(Howard:)No, after my tongue has swollen
to the size of a brisket.
All right, just let me get my keys.
(Howard:)Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God...
(Howard:)The laundry is out of the hamper.